If you have been looted
then hello I am your friend Vishwanath
so friends now before making the video
please see the disclaimer before watching the video friends it is
given in the description box so
if you start a business as per my wish
then its profit and loss is your own
responsibility my channel will
not have any responsibility you can invest in your play store
friends so today
definitely press the like button friends you can subscribe
friends if you
like it then definitely like subscribe in the comment and
ICICI Lombard
Insurance Company Limited crush you this is currently
in discussion friends in this now
it is matching access from India
such Aslam Barmer okay friends so this will become the
third largest
insurance company of India friends general
insurance is sitting friends so now we
see ICICI Lombard General
Insurance Company has
closed on Friday in NSE it closed at 21.05 that is from
- 560 friends and with 65 to see it
it had closed at 53 percent so you see the
feedback here friends the
same is of seven five and yes this  If you look at it, it's
going to test 1430.
Friends, you can get at least a 200-
point gain here if you
invest. Okay, friends. And
I think this method is different. This
polythene will be reported within the country
within two days.
Friends, it will touch 1540. And it's possible that it will touch at
least 500 on Monday. You'll see that the latest news is
coming, friends, that this Indian Defense
General Insurance is getting patients in the ward.
Friends, so this is very
good news, friends, you
can invest in it. Okay, friends. And if you
go short, friends, then the
scientific company is also starting a kind of team
GPS. Friends, Vikram
will see that the promoter's building has increased
- two per cent in quantum on a
quarterly basis. And if you look at the opportunity,
friends, are the brokers or greats making
recommendations or not? Their recommendation was,
let's say, 1290. Now that recommendation has started at 15.
Friends, this recommendation has increased.
You have given it, it is doing great, it is growing, friends, if
you look at the stock then it is running at a high speed right now, the price of the stock is
also high, friends, the thing which is more than
half the price, that is, it is more than the price, then
we consider it to be high,
friends, okay,
due to this price being high, its rate is also going down right now,
okay friends, if it comes down a little then definitely
buy it, friends, now here there are dead
technical experts, they are not showing profit, let's look at the
valuation, friends, the
company which is elevation here is a
company worth 1000 crores by market capitalization, friends,
see, I told you, you are getting five here, so here
comes 137 industries page 94
151 and subscribe to this point,
fifty five percent is being delivered,
here to see the community stunt,
hundred percent is being done, friends,
people here we are talking about Prince
and after that we go friends, here
its valuation has been done, okay
now we go to its friendship status,
so see here friends, if we
see his tomato monk in pension status, then the market which is
March  The sales of the one which was in 120
was 19.47 and in June it got consumed by
15.47, friends if we
take these into consideration then the figure was 21.11 and in June 2017
it became
306, which
increased to 31.04 in 2015, okay
now we will make the net profit 21.98 in March
20, but by the time June came, it became
101, friends,
its yes,
yes, so the pension status power of that,
my system is
going a little down, okay
friends, so
now let's see, I have taken a
fancy look at the share holding pattern here,
now let's see the share holding pattern, so
see friends, I am making this video short
because what happens by becoming too big is that
you people get bored, that's why I am
making it absolutely short, so
if we see its promoter holding,
then see its promoter holding in December,
friends, whatever  The promoter is
not withdrawing his assets, okay 55.67, no, he is
not investing right now, if he withdraws then
how will he do it, friends, it is exactly like that, friends, it is 50.86, it was a
very good team, the
growth of the product on the ticket is very good,
friends, okay, from here
we are getting to know that the stock is very good,
okay, it is a very small one,
if you look at the investment of around 3.199, the total
investment
holding is given, 15.09, pension institute has
folded point one to mutual fund
investment 10.47 one and a half point five and
pain 5.6, this way, this is the
share holding pattern, and after this,
I have also shown you a little indication of the company, the
company is very good, friends,
invest in it, you should know that now it is in the news,
friends, hence, at least ₹50 will
increase, friends, on Monday, okay, at least
₹50 will become, okay, because it is
in the news right now, friends, so whatever
news comes  So friends, you are a great devotee, if the
stock is okay then this trick is very good,
you should add it to your account and
invest it with the help of your financial advisor,
friends, okay and if you liked the video then definitely
press the like button, friends, you
can also comment, friends, those who want to
open a demat account, the link is
given below, you can go there and click on the link and get it
opened by clicking on that link,
friends, and those who want to be
added to the group, friends, my WhatsApp group is
written below, join it free of cost,
in this both the letters Nippon Pants are
given in Delhi Vidhansabha and stock
Kabir and free of cost, so you should definitely get added to it,
okay friends, thank you.